https://www.barbizon.com/barbizoncom_privacy_policy.html

Hi Guest!
Sign In
0
Current Location: WorldwideAtlantaBostonCharlotteChicagoDallasDenverNew YorkOrlandoPhoenixWashington, D.C.Barbizon Europe Limited
Equipment, Expendables, Systems, and Rigging for Entertainment and Architectural Lighting Since 1947
x
Thanks for your interest in the Barbizon Lighting Company.
You can sign up for one or more of our Barbizon mail lists below.
Sid & Sam's Overstock Updates
Which of our offices do you use most?
Phoenix
Washington D.C.
National Television Sales
Bangalore, India
London, UK
x
Thanks for taking the time to look further into how the Barbizon Lighting Company can help you!
So we can best serve you, there's a brief form below, fill it out and we'll forward it to the office and department best suited for your need.
If this is a little more than you need right now you can also click HERE to close this dialog so you can look around.
We look forward to being a valued resource to you!
State
InternationalAlaskaAlabamaArkansasArizonaCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDistrict of ColumbiaDelawareFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIowaIdahoIllinoisIndianaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMassachusettsMarylandMaineMichiganMinnesotaMissouriMississippiMontanaNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNebraskaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNevadaNew YorkOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaVermontWashingtonWisconsinWest VirginiaWyoming
Work Phone
Cell Phone
I am interested in the following:
Fixtures
Consumables
Lighting Systems (Dimming & Control)
Rigging
Energy Efficient Lighting
Technical Services
Describe how we can help i.e. it's something other than the above choices:
Help Center
Employee DirectoryWhere We AreRequest More InfoTechnical Services RequestTerms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyGovernment Sales
Show Reports
LDI 2019NAB 2019LDI 2018NAB 2018LDI 2017NAB 2017LDI 2016NAB 2016LDI 2015Tradeshow
Tags
20KAccessoriesAcoustic ControlAdaptorsAppsArchitectural ControlArchitectural Lightingarea lightingArriAudioBatteriesbi-colorBroadcastCable ManagementCable reelsCablesCamera BagsCamera LightingCamera SliderCamera SupportCamerasCartscasesclampsColor meterCommunicationCommunicationsConnectorsConsolesControlCue LightsCyc LightsdiffusersDimmingDisplay lighringDisplay LightingDistributiondistroDMXDollyDrop CeilingEffectseffects lightingElectrical Distributionequipment protectionEvent LightingFabricFilm LightingFiltersFixture AccessoriesFlexibleFlooringFog/SmokeFollow SpotsFollowspotsFresFresnelFresnelsFull colorFull spectrumgafferGriphardwareHMIHMI ReplacementHouse LightingHouse LightsIEMsinflatableInkieIntercomIP RatedIP65LampsLEDLED LightingLED RetrofitLED TapeLED TubesLighting ControlsLocation lightingMedia ServerMedia ServersMicrophonesMonopodMoving LightsMuseum LightingNetworkNetworkingpanelPanel Lightpipe gridPOEProfile FixturesProjectionprojection surfacesRabbit EarsReferencereference chartsRelay panelrelaysRGBWRiggingSafetyScreensscrimsSet ConstructionSetsShow ControlSkypanelsoft boxesSoft LightSoftlightsoftwarespacelightSpecial FXstorageStrobeTelevision LightingTesting EquipmentToolstripodsTrusstunable whiteUV/BlacklightVari-whiteVideoVideo ConferencingVideo Controlvideo edge blendingVideo Lightingvideo scalersVideo wall processorsvideo wallsWash LightsWeather protectionWeather resistantWirelessWireless DMXWireless MicrophonesWorklight
Barbizon.com Privacy Policy
This privacy statement covers the site Barbizon.com. We are committed to respecting and maintaining the privacy of our clients and visitors, and wish to demonstrate that commitment by adherence to the following policy. This policy defines the following topics:
What personally identifiable information Barbizon collects.
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
What organization collects the information.
How Barbizon uses the information.
With whom Barbizon may share user information.
What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Barbizon control.
How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection and Use
Information Collection
Barbizon is the sole owner of the information collected on webmaster@Barbizon.com. Barbizon collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.
Event Registration
To use online registration on this Web site for a Barbizon-sponsored event, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about changes to the event for which he has expressed interest. Information specific to the event, especially on the forms labeled, 'SPECIAL,' is optional, but highly recommended for the event.
Guestbook:Newsletter Subscription
To subscribe to our newsletter, user's are required to give a name and email address. This allows the newsletter synopsis page to be e-mailed to users.
Information Use
Profile
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and clear gifs to create a composite profile of our users. Profile information stored includes as a minimum the name, e-mail address, business type and preferences on receiving information by e-mail (newsletter and news releases). Through the business type, this information is joined to newsletter content and news releases to record a composite view of specific business types' content preferences. Profile information is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. Your profile is shared in aggregate form only.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.
The cookies set by the site flag a user as having the Macromedia Flash plug-in; identify if the user has seen a particular cartoon sequence on main pages, and provide business type information for content metrics on newsletter articles and news releases. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the "Profile" section.
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)
We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs in the e-mail synopsis page of the newsletter are tied to users' personally identifiable information, in that they pass a unique user ID back to the server to enable setting (or reading) a cookie.
In addition, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section.
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify profile information. Established members who have subscribed to the newsletter or news releases will receive regular mailings. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
Customer Service
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
Sharing
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and clients. This information consists of correlating survey results or article reading preferences with business types. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information. We DO NOT Share Personal Information with Third Parties.
Business Transitions
In the event Barbizon goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email and a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an "opt-out" mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications clicking on the link at the bottom of the message, or by emailing us at webmaster@Barbizon.com with 'UNSUBSCRIBE' in the subject line, or the user may contact us at .
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Barbizon, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Surveys
From time to time our site requests information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
phone: 212-586-1620
email: webmaster@Barbizon.com
Copyright © 2020 Barbizon Lighting CompanyTel: 866-502-2724
Site Developed by: Crescit Software, Inc.
